请说明一下43页第七节
Page 43, section 7. We'd like some clarification.
第七节是是关于评估手段
Section 7 has to do with the evaluative measures--
评估手段
"Evaluative measures."
这就是教师绩效标准
What we're talking about here are performance standards,
简单明了
plain and simple.
这是不行的  是在自寻烦恼
We can't have that. We open that can of worms--
-得删掉它  弗兰克  -政府要加上这点
- Gotta take it out, Frank. - The Administration wants it in.
那我们就是在浪费时间
Then we're all wasting our time.
我可以降低考核频率
Well, look, I can cut down the frequency of testing,
但它必须留在法案里
but it's got to be part of the overall--
恶果会滚雪球
That's the thin edge of a two-ton wedge.
-这不行  没得商量  -等等
- No way, non-debatable. - All right, hold on.
听他们说完也没坏处  对吧
There's no harm in hearing them out, right?
弗兰克  你怎么想
Frank, what do you have in mind?
我们修正第四条  给我第四条
We adjust article 4. Hand me article 4.
两年一次改为三年
We go every three years instead of two.
弗兰克  要我们考虑考核...
Frank, for us to even consider testing--
马蒂  这根本就不是频率的问题
Marty, we can't negotiate time intervals here.
我只是说如果这么做
If-- I'm just saying if--
频率决不能高于五年一次
The frequency could never be more than five years.
五年一次有点低  但如果这你们同意了
Look, five is a little high, but if you can bend on that--
-马蒂  -等等  这不光是频率问题
- Marty. - Wait, wait, wait. And it's not just frequency.
如果资深教师
Veteran teachers would have to be exempt
教学成绩斐然  他们可以免考
if they have a proven record of excellence with the students.
我得失陪一下
Well, excuse me for a moment.
科瑞  你来说一下这个问题
Corey, will you take the reins on this?
好  第四条  关于免考
Right, so, article 4-- in terms of exceptions--
多年来  我一直说这东西该拆掉
I've been saying for years that we should tear it down.
少女遭遇不幸  郡长指责国会议员
不仅土气  让全郡都丢脸
It's vulgar, it's an embarrassment to the county,
但弗兰克・安德伍德却一次次
but time and time again Frank Underwood
拼力保住它
has fought to keep it standing.
如果不是他
If it weren't for him,
大桃子早就被改建了
the Peachoid would've been replaced ages ago.
杰西卡・马斯特斯也不会死去
And Jessica Masters would still be alive.
国会议员要为这起悲剧负责
The congressman needs to answer for this tragedy.
究竟发生了什么
What exactly happened?
一名17岁的女孩
A 17-year-old girl
驾车跟男友发短信而冲出大路  短信为
ran off the road texting her boyfriend, and I quote,
"大桃子像不像个巨大的..."
"Doesn't the Peachoid look like a giant..."
-然后她的车就失控了  -老天
- And then she lost control of the car. - Jesus.
奥林利用当地媒体大做文章
Orrin's making a big fuss in the local press.
他还催促女孩父母起诉加夫尼郡
And he's pushing the parents to sue Gaffney.
起诉加夫尼  那是他的辖区啊
Sue Gaffney? It's in his own jurisdiction.
为了把你拖下水
It's worth throwing Gaffney under the bus
他在所不辞
to drag you into the mess.
他又在觊觎我的位子
He's after my seat again.
就没吸取丁点教训吗
Has he learned absolutely nothing?
这是火力全开的诋毁宣传  先生
It's a full-on smear campaign, boss.
他想毁了你
He's out to destroy you.
用这个  天呐  不就是个桃子吗
With this? It's a peach, for Christ sake.
让他自己出丑吧
Let him make a fool out of himself.
不  他会让你出丑的
No, he will make a fool out of you.
如果他炒作得当  报道覆盖全国
If he spins this right, gets national coverage--
覆盖全国  这就是个笑话
National coverage? It's a joke.
到时候  你就成笑柄了
And you will be the butt of it.
我们现在不能出事
We can't afford that right now,
你现在因为教育法案正备受瞩目
not when you're in the spotlight with the education bill.
这事给我惹了这么多麻烦
This thing has caused me so much damn trouble.
-我知道  -我该打给谁  女孩父母吗
- I know. - So who should I call, parents?
打电话是不够的
Phone call's not going to cut it.
-你得亲自南下  -不能等到周一吗
- You need to go down there. - Can it wait until Monday?
我们马上处理此事  还能控制得住
We get on this thing right now, we can contain it.
如果等到周一
We wait until Monday,
那就难说这事会造成多大的破坏
then there's no way to know how much this is going to blow up on us.
我不能南下去加夫尼  工会刚
I can't go down to Gaffney. The unions have just--
-我们延期  -他们会发火的
- We postpone-- - They're gonna be livid.
马蒂通事理  会和他们解释的
Marty's reasonable, okay? He will explain to them.
那他们就能理解并接受
And they're just supposed to understand and accept
我不得不中断谈判
that I had to get up from the negotiating table
只因一个小郡长想...
because some two-bit county administrator wants to--
我不想打断你  先生
I don't want to interrupt you, sir,
但这不只是关于奥林
but this is not just about Orrin.
还有女孩的父母
It's about the parents.
你想想诉讼
Now, you think about the lawsuit.
如果要你去做证怎么办
What happens if you have to testify?
传票  宣誓作证
Subpoenas, depositions.
你要是被卷入官司
You get dragged into a court battle,
就别提教育法案了
there is no education bill.
这事不容忽视
We can't ignore this.
小球战术  积累小分  打乱对手节奏
我讨厌这套扯淡的"小球战术"
I just hate this small-ball crap.
叫什么  桃什么
It's called the what? The peach what?
大桃子
The Peachoid.
那是一座桃子状的巨型水塔
It's a giant water tower in the shape of a peach.
我刚谷歌了  大桃子
I just googled it. "The Peachoid."
她才17岁  琳达
She was 17, Linda.
没错  抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
-再给我一周时间  -这不行
- I need another week. - No, that's not going to work.
总统要在周二做演说
The president makes his speech on Tuesday.
我们已经宣布了
We've already announced.
演说可以重新安排
Speeches can be rescheduled.
教改得拿出进展来  弗兰克
We have to show some progress on education, Frank.
就职百天转眼就到
The first hundred days is almost over.
如果我们推迟演说
If we push back the speech,
会让人觉得我们在偷懒
it'll look like we're spinning our wheels.
好吧  我再想想办法
All right, I'll work something out.
谢谢  琳达
Thank you, Linda.
弗兰克  这些人是
Frank, these are the heads
全国最大的两个教师工会的首脑
of the two largest teachers unions in the country.
-我明白  -他们周末抽空飞过来的
- I understand. - They flew here on a weekend.
道格会主持讨论
Doug will lead the charge.
菲利普斯议员也没问题
Congressman Phillips is well vetted--
他们是飞来见你的  弗兰克
They flew here to see you, Frank.
是你在负责法案
You're managing this bill.
把这放到那个包里
Put this in the other bag.
我会保持联络的
And I'll be in constant communication.
有什么要紧事  打电话就行了
Anything big comes up, I'm a phone call away.
300页的文件啊
It's a 300-page document.
我们需要你在场
We need you in that room.
我也是没办法
I would stay if I could,
这可是我的选区啊
but this is my home district.
马蒂  放我一马吧
Now, Marty, cut me a little slack here.
我们能把它搞定
We'll get it done.
我们是老交情了
You and I go way back.
我让你失望过吗
Have I ever let you down?
没  没有
No, you haven't.
我现在也没这打算
And I don't intend to start now.
有人吗
Hello?
新项目关注水资源问题
-吉莉安吗  -克莱尔
- Gillian? - Claire.
很高兴终于见面了
It's so nice to finally meet you.
我有点身体不适
Yeah-- I'm a little under the weather.
不想传染给你
I don't want to get you sick.
你要是不舒服  我们可以...
Well, if you're feeling ill, we can--
不不不  没关系  感冒而已
No, no, no, I'm fine. It's just a cold.
非常感谢你过来
Well, thank you for coming in.
不客气
Of course.
去我办公室谈好吗
Shall we talk in my office?
这些照片真棒
These are really cool photographs.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
是亚当・嘉乐威拍的
Adam Galloway took the pictures.
你听说过他吗
Have you heard of him?
没有
No.
惠特尼双年展: 旨在推动美国前卫艺术的展会
我几年前在惠特尼双年展上遇到他
I met him at the Whitney biennial a couple years ago
54%的饮用水相关疾病是由未处理地下水造成的
然后委托他拍了这些
and commissioned him to do these.
PS1: 美国最大  年代最久的非营利性艺术中心  位于纽约长岛
他刚刚在PS1开了大型摄影展
He just had a big show at PS1.
我对艺术界真的不太了解
I'm not up to date on the art world.
没关系
That's all right.
我们也不是来谈论摄影的  不是吗
We're not here to talk about photography. Are we?
我办公室在这边
My office is over here.
遇到任何麻烦  打电话给我
You run into any trouble, you call me.
没问题的
I got it covered.
吉恩・克兰希知道我要过去吗
Gene Clancy know I'm coming?
刚刚和他通过话
Just spoke to him.
那就去吧
Get to it.
你的航班定好了  55分后起飞
Your flight is booked, leaves in 55 minutes.
艾德会跟你过去
Ed will be joining you.
史蒂夫去哪了
Where's Steve?
他一小时前请病假回家了  先生
He went home sick about an hour ago, sir.
我来顶替他
I'll be filling in.
你叫什么来着  姓什么
What's your name again? Edward what?
-密查姆  -你开车快吗  密查姆
- Meacham. - You drive fast, Meacham?
你找我吗
You wanted to talk to me?
进来  佐伊  这位是蒂尔顿太太...
Come on, Zoe. This is Mrs. Tilden, owner of--
她知道我是谁
She knows who I am.
蒂尔顿太太很喜欢你对凯瑟琳・杜兰特的特写
Mrs. Tilden liked your profile on Catherine Durant.
不  不是喜欢  是非常喜欢
No, I didn't. I loved it.
有深度  非常坚定
In depth, uncompromising.
通常我不会在报道付印前阅读
Normally I don't read things before they go to print,
但凯茜是我的朋友
but Cathy's a friend.
说说你是怎么提前知道她会获提名的
Tell me how you knew she'd be nominated before she did?
你想知道我的消息来源
You want my source?
汤姆说你不肯告诉他
Tom says you won't tell him.
我谁也没告诉
I haven't told anyone.
我是报社的东家
Well, I own the paper.
能在这里工作我深感荣幸
And I'm very grateful to be working here.
那你也不准备告诉我了
So you're not going to tell me either.
您想要什么  我的联络人还是气节
Which do you want, my source or my integrity?
汤姆
Tom.
把佐伊的报道挪到周日的头版
Move Zoe's piece to the front page of Sunday's edition.
我会考虑的
Let me think that over.
随你怎么考虑
You think it over as much as you want.
然后把它放在头版
Then put it on the front page.
为了让世界之井站稳脚跟我付出了很大努力
I've worked really hard to gain a foothold with World Well.
六年前  只有我自己和一台笔记本
Six years ago it was just me and a macbook.
我明白
I understand.
打了两份临时工才付得起房租
And I had to juggle two temp jobs just to pay the rent.
那是你的孩子  你不想放手
It's your baby. You don't want to let it go.
我只是...
Well, I just--
你也不必放手  吉莉安
And you wouldn't have to, Gillian.
我只希望你把亲手建立的事业发展壮大
All I want is for you to grow what you've already built.
我听说你裁掉了一半员工
I heard you fired half your staff.
是的
Yes, I did.
这让我很担心
That worries me.
我让他们走是为给你腾位置
I let them go to make room for you.
我不确定我们是否合适
I'm just not sure we're the right match.
说实话  我不太愿意
To be honest, I'm a little uncomfortable
跟一个雇得起著名摄影师的人共事
working with someone who's commissioning famous photographers
我都付不起我志愿者的公车票
when I can't even buy my volunteers bus fair to the office.
你知道妮姬・海姆勒吗
Do you know who Nicky Hemler is?
-不  -妮姬拥有切尔西最大的画廊
- No. - Nicky owns one of the biggest galleries in Chelsea.
她十分想作亚当・嘉乐威的代理人
She desperately wanted to represent Adam Galloway.
我帮她牵了线
I delivered on Adam,
作为回报
and in return
她每年给净水计划捐赠近4万美元
she contributes almost 40 grand a year to CWI.
这些钱用于作影响研究
That money goes to impact studies,
游说工作和调查
lobbying efforts, research.
这种钱对世界之井益处良多  吉莉安
World Well could benefit from that sort of money, Gillian,
而你的专长对我们益处良多
and we can benefit from your expertise.
我能想想吗
Can I think about it?
当然
Of course.
不必操之过急
We don't have to jump into anything.
我在这个小乡村长大
I grew up here, in the up country--
《圣经》  烧烤  沉重的负担
Bibles, barbecues, and broken backs.
这么靠南的地方  一切都更加浓郁
Everything gets just a little bit thicker this far south.
空气  血液  甚至我自己
The air, the blood, even me.
我尽量每个月过来一次
I try to make it down here at least once a month.
欢迎弗兰克・J・安德伍德议员来到南卡罗来纳州加夫尼
每次来都会提醒我走了多远
Every trip is a reminder of how far I've come.
小时候我讨厌加夫尼  那时我一无所有
I hated Gaffney as a kid, when I had nothing.
但现在我能够欣赏它
but now I've come to appreciate it.
它不像从前那样压抑难耐了
It's not as suffocating as it once was,
除了我要来处理这种让我想
except when I have to deal with the sort of nonsense
悬梁自尽的屁事的时候
that makes me want to hang myself.
路线一左转
Turn left on route one.
别听她的  我知道怎么走
Don't listen to her. I know a better way.
好的
Yes, sir.
我们没钱  弗兰克
We don't have the money, Frank.
单是诉讼费就够我们受的
The legal bills alone will kill us.
和解呢
How about a settlement?
我看钱数吧
I'll look at the numbers.
你说它像什么
What's it look like to you?
桃子
Like a peach.
我是说你到底怎么想的
No, I mean what does it really look like?
作为郡长  我还认定像桃子
As mayor, I stick with a peach.
作为老百姓
As a private citizen,
它看着像阳光照耀到了不该照到的地方
well, it looks like the sun is shining where it shouldn't be.
有更好的处理方法
There's a better way to handle this.
真的吗  弗兰克  什么方法
Really, Frank? And what's that?
我不是来吵架的
I'm not trying to start an argument here.
你说得好像我错了
You make it sound like I'm in the wrong.
不  你很清楚自己在做什么  奥林
No, you know exactly what you're doing, Orrin.
你利用这可怜女孩的死
You're using this poor girl's death
为自己谋政治利益
for your own political advantage.
我打算推倒水塔
You're the one that fought me
那些桃农怨声载道时
when the peach farmers bitched and moaned
是你跟我叫板
about me tearing it down.
是你拿了他们的钱
You're the one that took their money.
-只是个水塔  -是个荒唐的东西
- It's a water tower. - It's ungodly.
-奥林  -这是老生常谈了  弗兰克
- Orrin. - This is cut and dry, Frank.
我要推倒它
I fought to tear it down.
而你要留着它
You fought to keep it up.
那女孩的死是你的错
That girl's blood is on your hands,
我要你为之负责
and I'm taking you to task for it.
好吧  告诉你
All right, I'll tell you what.
迪克・彼得斯要卸任了
Dick Peters is going to retire this term.
就是说第四选区会有场公开竞选
That means there's an open race in the fourth district.
我帮你搞定那职位怎样
How about I help you lock up that seat?
我没想做交易  弗兰克
I'm not looking to make a deal, Frank.
这不是交易
It's not a deal.
是机遇
It's an opportunity.
算了吧
I'll be just fine.
你或许鄙视我  奥林
You may despise me, Orrin,
但邀请我们上去
but the classy thing to do
喝些冰茶
would've been to invite us up
才叫有气度
for some of that iced tea.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你不该在这儿跑步
You shouldn't run here.
真不知羞耻
It's disgraceful.
你不懂得尊重吗
Have you no respect?
考核标准是出发点
The criteria is a starting point.
只是建议  不是强制的
They're suggested, not mandated.
我们召集了专家智囊团
We assemble a council of experts
他们会定夺究竟...
who will determine exactly--
这里压根没说那些专家是谁
Nowhere here does it say who these experts are,
或如何甄选
how they'll be chosen.
总统亲自挑选
The president selects the council.
如何监管
What sort of oversight?
我们要参与甄选
We'd like input on the selection.
道格  联系琳达
Doug, check with Linda.
这就去
Calling her now.
好的  现在可以谈谈特许学校了吗
Okay, so now can we talk about charter schools?
特许学校不行
Charter schools are a no-go.
法案里必须有
They have to be in there.
保留他们  就别谈了
You keep them in, we walk.
我们也是
The same goes for us.
别急着下最后通牒
Let's not jump to ultimatums.
想办法减少对非公立学校的资助吧
Well, let's figure out a way to reduce non-public spending.
容我想几分钟
All right, give me a few minutes to think about that.
这事不说明白我们没法继续
We can't move forward without addressing this point.
我明白  但这是法案的基础啊
I understand, but this is the cornerstone of the bill.
那就谈谈吧
Let's talk it out.
给我五分钟  马蒂  马上回电
Give me five minutes, Marty. I'll call you right back.
不  别
No, no.
如果我们考虑和解
If we consider settlement as an option,
我们得付得起钱
we need to be able to pay for it.
但如果我们要和解
But if we offer a settlement,
-是不是  -我就这个意思
- aren't we saying... - That's my point.
我们等于承认小镇要为这孩子的死负责
We're admitting that the town's responsible for this kid's death.
要我说  让桃农付钱
I say make the peach farmers cough it up.
老天  那可要闹翻天了
Oh, man, talk about a shit storm.
麻烦说说谈到哪了
Y'all mind catchin' me up?
维恩和崔维斯想上法庭
Wayne and Travis want to go to court.
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think that's a good idea.
我们不能把钱砸到和解上
We can't be pouring money into a settlement
我们的钱都不够城市运营了
when we can barely afford to run the city.
吉恩  你怎么看
What do you think, gene?
我觉得我们该提防桃农协会
I think that we gotta worry about the peach farmers association.
我们哪怕流露出一点归咎于大桃子的意思
If there is a hint that we're blaming the Peachoid,
他们都会闹得不可开交
they're going to raise holy hell.
谁在乎啊  让他们都忍着
Who gives a crap. They gotta suck it up.
让他说完
Let him talk.
我就是说  得小心他们
I'm just saying that we need to keep them in mind.
她违法了  事情就是这样
She was breaking the law. End of story.
开车时不该发短信
You can't text while you drive.
但陪审团只会看到
Yeah, but all a jury's going to see
一个漂亮的花季少女现在死了
is a beautiful 17-year-old girl who's now dead.
无意冒犯  弗兰克  但你刚到这儿
No offense, Frank, but you just got here.
而我们已经讨论一个星期了
We've been dealing with this for the last week now.
那你们的解决方案呢
And where's your solution?
怎么
What?
你觉得你比我们厉害吗
You think you know better than us?
我只是想现实一点
I'm just trying to be realistic.
弗兰克  我知道你想从天而降  挽救大局
Frank, I know you want to swoop down and save the day,
但这事关原则
but there's a principle at stake here.
我们要是就为这种事被人敲诈...
We allow ourselves to be extorted because of this teenager--
等奥林找来陪审团为这女孩挥泪如雨
When Orrin gets a jury to weep a river of snot over this dead girl,
等加夫尼因为
when Gaffney goes tits up
付不起上百万的赔偿而破产
because you can't afford to pay a seven-figure award in damages,
等你们都被一脚踹出办公室
when you all get booted out of office
而我也输给蔡斯
and I lose to Chase,
那时你再来跟我唠叨你的原则
then you can chew my ear off about principles,
因为到时我们唯一不缺的就是时间
because we'll all have nothing but time on our hands.
在那之前
Until then,
你要么出力
you either contribute,
要么就闭嘴  崔维斯
or you keep it shut, Travis.
好了  我们这么办
Now, here's what we're going to do.
吉恩  如果必须和解
Gene, how much can we pull together
-我们能凑多少钱  -大约15万
- for a settlement if we had to? - About 150.
足够了  詹米  让你手下去五金店
That'll work. Jamie, get your boys down to the hardware store
造两块公告牌
to build two billboards.
放在塔两侧各一英里的地方
Put them out a mile out on either side of the tower.
写上"小心驾车  莫发短信"
Have them read, "Drive safely. No texting behind the wheel."
-知道了  -明早前完工
- Got it. - And get those up by tomorrow morning.
我来发许可证
I'll issue the permits.
以后晚上把塔上的灯熄了
And let's stop lighting the thing at night.
桃农不会高兴的
The peach farmers aren't going to like that.
开灯的话要多少电费
Well, how much does the electric cost?
每个月超过4100美元
4,100 plus change per month.
一年大约5万
About 50,000 a year.
天啊  都够供一个孩子上大学了
Jesus, you could put a kid through college on--
我们用这笔钱以她的名义办个奖学金
Let's use that money to start a scholarship fund in her name.
同时  你和桃农协会说
Meantime, you tell the association,
他们想晚上点亮它  就自己付电费
if they want it lit up, they can pay for it.
我很乐意传达这个消息
I'll deliver that message happily.
再给我拟一份拆掉"肛门"的计划和预算
And do me up a budget and a plan for removing the sphincter.
拆掉什么
The what?
他是指塔上的应急阀
He means the emergency valve.
有意思
That's interesting.
我一直觉得它长得像阴蒂
I always thought of it as a clitoris.
可那东西在底下啊
But it's on bottom.
阴蒂应该是在上面...
I believe the clitoris is above the--
但假设那女的是趴着的话
But if you imagine a woman on her belly--
行了  去做就是了
Enough. I want it done.
还有  吉恩  把所有交通条例都拿给我
And, Gene, give me everything you've got on road regulations.
要郡级章程  不要市级的
County statutes, not municipal.
你还记得上次选举我们叫停的
And do you remember that power line business
那个电力线工程吗
we pulled up at the last election?
当然
Sure do.
确保那事万无一失
Let's make sure we're rock solid on that.
这顿价值不菲的晚餐
Does this very expensive dinner
换得来一晚美妙的鱼水之欢吗
at least buy me an evening of mind-blowing sexual congress?
还不错  但也没那么好吧
It was good, but I don't know if it was that good.
好到可以口交吗
Fellatio good?
也许给你打个手枪  不能保证
Hand job maybe. No promises.
也行
Deal.
彼得  我有事情和你说
Okay, um, Peter, there's something I need to tell you.
我最近一直在想
I have been thinking lately.
换个工作可能会是好事
You know, um, it might be good to work somewhere else.
我参加了几次面试
So I did some interviews,
议长办公室请我做人力分配部副主管
and the speaker's office offered me deputy LD.
彼得
Peter.
克里斯蒂娜
Christina, um--
我觉得这挺好的  对吧
I just thought it could be good, right,
如果我们要发展下去
if we're going to have any future,
结束上下级恋情  成为真正的情侣
to stop this boss-staffer thing and be a real couple.
我们就是情侣啊
We are a real couple.
我是指不用再在办公室遮遮掩掩的
I mean not have to hide it like we do at the office.
而且这个机会很不错
And it's a great opportunity.
那可是议长
The speaker?
如果我接了这份工作  你会怨我吗
Would you hate me if I took the job?
宝贝  你想要的就是我想要的
Baby, I want what you want.
我没有  我不会反对你
I'm not-- I won't fight you on this,
只要这是你想要的
not if this is what you feel you need to do.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
你说得对
And you're right.
这是个好机会
This is a great opportunity.
你要什么时候给他们答复
When do you have to tell them by?
没设期限  我不用马上就做决定
There's no deadline. I don't have to decide right away.
那行  等你决定了
Okay, well, when you decide,
记得帮我找个人接替你
just, you know, help me find a replacement.
提前通知我一声
You know, give me a heads-up.
当然
Yeah, of course.
我还没决定要不要接受那份工作呢
I haven't even decided if I'm going to take it.
我们不用急着讨论这事
We don't have to talk this through right now.
我只是觉得应该跟你提一下
I just-- I just thought I'd bring it up.
-我们回家啊  -好极了
- Should we get out of here? - Yes.
咱们去找那对父母吧
Let's go find the parents.
你就在这儿守着
You hang back by the car.
那里人很多  先生
It's a big crowd, sir.
如果我安慰一对悲痛的父母时中枪或遇刺
If I get shot or stabbed consoling two grieving parents,
那么我将流芳千古
I'm a hero from now until the end of time.
我们赌一把吧  好吗
Let's roll the dice. Shall we?
先生  我不能允许你只身走入人群
Sir, I can't allow you to go unescorted into all those people.
允许我
Allow me?
有件事我们得说清楚  密查姆
Let's get one thing straight, Meacham.
我能做什么不能做什么  这你管不着
You are never to dictate what I can and cannot do.
我吩咐你做事的时候
The only two words I want to hear from you
只想听到两个词
when I ask you to do something
"是的"还有"先生"
are "Yes" and "Sir."
明白了吗
Is that understood?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
很好  我们会相处融洽的
Good. Then we're gonna get along just fine.
马斯特斯先生和太太
Mr. and Mrs. Masters,
我是本区议员弗兰克・安德伍德
I'm Frank Underwood, your congressman.
请二位节哀顺变
I'm so sorry for your loss.
我无法体会
I cannot begin to fathom--
没错  你不能  你完全无法体会
You're right. You can't. You have no idea.
请原谅  我无意打扰  只是想
Forgive me. I don't mean to intrude. I just--
-你已经打扰到我们了  -迪恩  别这样
- Well, you are intruding. - Dean, please.
怎么了
What?
这全怪他  不是吗
It's his fault. Isn't it?
不管怎样  我只是想表示哀悼
Anyway, I just wanted to express my condolences,
如果两位有任何需要
and say if there's anything the two of you nee--
迪恩  你不会想跟他谈的
Dean, you don't want to be talking to him.
我们会诉诸法律
We got legal action pending.
我知道蔡斯先生的看法  也相信
Look, I know what Mr. Chase has been saying, and believe--
没人邀请你来
Nobody invited you.
没人需要你的哀悼或是借口
Nobody wants your condolences or your excuses.
弗兰克  你走吧
Frank, please.
你现在不该承受这些
You shouldn't have to put up with this right now.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
进展顺利啊
Well, that went well.
等一下
Hang on a second.
牧师先生
Reverend.
议员先生
Congressman.
见到你真好
Nice to see you again.
真希望情况不是这个样子
I wish it was under better circumstances.
真是可怕的惨剧
Terrible, isn't it?
太不幸了
It's just terrible.
你组织这场活动真是费心了
This is so thoughtful what you've organized here.
绵薄之力罢了
Least we can do.
马斯特斯一家是你的教众吗
Tell me, are the Masters in your congregation?
是的  他们每周日都来
They are. They come every Sunday.
他们明天也会去做礼拜吗
Do you think they'll be at the service tomorrow?
一定会的
I'd be surprised if they weren't.
能帮我个忙吗
I'm wondering can you do me a favor?
什么都行  弗兰克
Anything for you, Frank.
蓝色的牙刷是你的  对吧
Oh, the blue toothbrush is yours, right?
对  蓝色的
Uh, yeah, the blue one.
-彼得  -什么事
- Hey, Peter? - Yeah?
你把灯泡放哪了
Where do you keep the light bulbs?
卧室的灯不亮了
The lamp in the bedroom is out.
在厨房水槽下面
In the kitchen, under the sink.
我是这么想的
Here's what I think.
我也希望自己能大度一些  但我做不到
I wish I could be bigger than this, but I can't,
我这么做很自私
and I'm being selfish,
而且也只顾着自己  但管它呢
and I realize it's mostly about me, but fuck it.
我必须说出来
I have to say it.
请不要接受那份工作  克里斯蒂娜
Please don't take that other job, Christina.
反正  我就是这么想的
Anyway, that's how I feel.
很高兴你告诉我了
I'm glad you told me.
特许学校危及我们的组织能力
Charters jeopardize our ability to organize,
这个理由就足够了
which is reason enough,
但更大的问题是
but the bigger issue is
以他们的绩效
that measuring their success--
特许学校一直遵行的
Charters schools have operated
评估标准  无异于任何...
under the same evaluative standards that every--
不同事物  区别对待
Apples and oranges.
不论从哪个角度出发
No matter how you look at it,
都不能用同一套标准去衡量
you can't use the same standards to compare.
你是在说
What, you're advocating a
特效学校的考核标准应该更严格吗
more demanding criteria for charter schools than other schools--
我们的意思很简单  弗兰克
Our point is simple, Frank.
有些款项只能拨给
Several funds should only go
-联邦公立学校  -等一下
- to public union school districts - Hold on a second.
但我们已经将非特许学校的拨款增加了一成
Yeah, but we've already increased non-charter funding by 10%.
拨给特许学校的款项根本微不足道
The amount going to charter schools is negligible.
这事没有先例  弗兰克  与数目无关
It's the precedent, Frank, not the number.
我们要开启很多先例  马蒂
We're setting a lot of precedents, Marty.
这才叫改革
That's the nature of reform.
有些可以忍受  有些不能忍
Well, some of them we can stomach. Some of them we can't.
我们别纠结于这些模糊的问题了
All right, let's not get bogged down in abstractions.
谈一下具体事宜吧
Let's deal with specifics.
科瑞  带我们从头理一遍吧
Corey, can you walk us through it?
确定拨款的数额
There's a three-prong approach
要采用三分法...
to determining the amount of funding...
想我了吗
Miss me?
也许有一点
Maybe. A little.
我们分开多久了  有15个小时吗
What's it been, 15 hours?
短到我都没发觉你离开了
Not even long enough to notice you're gone.
马蒂・斯比奈拉也这么想就好了
Tell that to Marty Spinella.
进展如何了
How's it coming?
进展缓慢而痛苦
It's coming. Slowly, painfully.
我们家前院里一直种着郁金香吗
Hey, have we always had tulips in the front yard,
还是我脑子不好使了
or am I slowly going insane?
我去年秋天种的
I planted them last fall.
你没有
You did not.
我跟你一起去那儿为选举做宣传的时候
When I was down with you for the campaign.
你这辈子都没碰过花花草草
You've never gardened a day in your life.
不对  我这辈子刚好侍弄过一天花花草草
Not true. I have gardened exactly one day in my life.
你当时在斯帕坦堡筹集资金
You were down in Spartanburg doing some sort of fundraiser.
吉恩妻子带着一篮子球茎来看我
Gene's wife came over with a bucket of bulbs,
接着我就跪在泥巴里
and next thing you knew, I was down on my knees in the dirt,
和蚯蚓为伴了
earthworms and all.
我简直无法想象
I can't even picture it.
我也不能  我还是当事人呢
Neither can I, and I was there.
说说别的
What else?
让我别去想大桃子和死去的少女
Distract me from giant peaches and dead teenagers.
说什么呢
What else?
我今天去跑步了
Oh, I went for a run today,
发生了件奇怪的事
and the strangest...
说不清楚  有个女人
I-- I don't know. This woman...
-有意思  -怎么了
- That's interesting. - What is?
-佐伊・巴恩斯刚发来一条短信  -谁
- Oh, a text just came. Zoe Barnes. - Who?
佐伊  68小时23分钟11秒
你那晚见过的那个《先驱报》记者
Oh, that reporter from the herald you met one night.
我记得她
Oh, her. I remember.
要是需要给她回电话你就挂了吧
Yeah, go if you need to call her back.
不用  她可以等
No, she can wait.
我可在和我妻子通话
I'm talking to my wife.
没关系  反正我也要去睡了
That's okay. I'm going to bed soon anyway.
明天见
See you tomorrow?
希望如此  祝我好运
I hope so. Wish me luck.
晚安  我的小桃子
Mm, bonsoir, my petite Peachoid.
真恶心
Disgusting.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
好的  没问题  科瑞  马蒂
Yeah, all right, that's fine, Corey. Marty?
弗兰克  我给你解释一下  问题在这儿
Frank, let me explain it to you. Here's our problem.
弗兰克・安德伍德  什么意思
佐伊  我们有这么久没通话了
佐伊  你在哪
佐伊  在干什么
佐伊  接下来会怎么样
佐伊  告诉我
弗兰克・安德伍德  南卡罗来纳  选区事务
佐伊  方便说话吗
弗兰克・安德伍德  现在不行  正在忙
佐伊  还有什么事能比我还急
弗兰克・安德伍德  你真是不可抵挡
佐伊  不可抵挡  我还没开始呢
弗兰克・安德伍德  我简直无法想象
佐伊  你肯定想象得到
佐伊  你肯定已经想过了
佐伊  看明天的《出发点》  我会飞个吻给你
弗兰克  弗兰克  你断线了吗
Frank? Frank, did we lose you?
我在听  马蒂
Uh, yeah, I'm here, Marty.
听着  我们可以就特许学校的事继续兜圈子
Look, we can talk ourselves in circles about charter schools,
但我建议这样做
but here's what I propose.
佐伊・巴恩斯访谈
在你的人物特写里  你对杜兰特职业生涯早期
In your profile, you go into great detail
所面对的性别歧视进行了很细致的描述
about the sexism Durant faced early on in her career.
没错
That's right.
她最初当选的时候
When she was first elected,
参议院还是男人的世界
it was still an old boy's club in the senate.
不久之前  新闻业也是一样的
Journalism used to be that way, too, not so long ago.
我真的感到很幸运
I feel really lucky.
我前面有很多的开拓者
I've had lots of trailblazers come before me.
比如我的同事  简宁・斯克斯基
For instance, my colleague Janine Skorsky
是《先驱报》首位
was the first woman at the herald
成为首席政治记者的女性
to become chief political correspondent,
而那距今也只有五年
and that was only five years ago.
是那些开拓者
Has it been those trailblazers
让你晋升得如此迅速吗
who've allowed you to rise so quickly?
你从都市板块
You've moved up from the Metro pages
走上了周日的头版
to the front page Sunday edition.
如果不是有简宁在前铺路
Uh, well, I don't know that that would be possible
我恐怕是做不到这一切的
if Janine hadn't already paved the way.
这是否意味着
So does that mean that
《先驱报》不够进步
the herald is not particularly progressive?
我认为够进步了  汤姆的思想很开放
I think that they are. Tom is very open minded.
简宁能获得升职也是因为他
He's the reason Janine got promoted.
我们说的是汤姆・汉默施密特  执行主编
That's Tom Hammerschmidt, the executive editor.
没错  我们都叫他锤子
Yes, we actually call him the hammer.
锤子  为什么
The hammer? Why?
因为他很严厉
Because he's tough.
有多严厉
How tough?
他  汤姆有很高的标准
He's, uh-- Tom has very high standards.
我很爱他
I love him.
他是位伟大的导师
He's a-- he's a great mentor.
不过有时会让人觉得沮丧
Um, it can be frustrating at times.
他会让你反复核查稿件
Um, he makes you double and triple-check things,
而你一拿到新闻就急着想发表
and you want to get the news out the moment you have it,
而他会让你不断修改  直到完美
and he makes you rewrite until it's perfect,
但正是这份严谨成就了《先驱报》
but that's what makes the Herald the Herald.
这种模式在网络时代依然可行吗
Is that a workable model in the Internet age?
我们的读者认为可行
Our readers think it is.
可你们的读者人数在下滑
Well, you have a declining readership.
但我不认为这是汤姆的责任
But I don't lay that at Tom's feet.
我们所处的时代就是如此  不是吗
I think that that's the times we live in, right?
报纸应该迎合我们所处的时代吗
Should newspapers adapt to the times we live in?
《先驱报》并没有拒绝改变
It's not that the Herald refuses to adapt.
我们有网络版
We have an online presence.
那会不会是你们改变得不够快
Is that maybe not adapting fast enough?
我不会反驳这一观点
I wouldn't argue with that statement.
我们可以更加努力
We could do more.
我们今天有一位特别来宾
We've got a special guest with us today.
他请求能借今早的机会
He asked for the opportunity
和大家说几句话
to share a few words with us this morning--
有请本区国会议员  弗兰克・安德伍德
Our very own congressman, Frank Underwood.
-早上好  -早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
谢谢你  牧师
Thank you, reverend,
也感谢唱诗班带来的美妙圣歌
and thanks to that choir for that beautiful hymn.
我今天早上想读的内容  是...
I want to read, this morning, from...
不
No.
有一个话题人人回避
You know what no one wants to talk about.
恨
Hate.
我非常了解恨
I know all about hate.
它在你腹中酝酿
It starts in your gut,
在你体内深处
deep down here,
搅动翻腾
where it stirs and churns.
接着它涌起
And then it rises.
恨意猛烈而迅猛地上升
Hate rises fast and volcanic.
令人冲口而出激动的话语
It erupts hot on the breath.
你怒目圆睁  充满怒火
Your eyes go wide with fire.
你咬紧牙关
You clench your teeth so hard
简直要咬碎牙齿
you think they'll shatter.
我恨你  上帝  我恨你
I hate you, God. I hate you!
别说你们从没说过这句话
Oh, don't tell me you haven't said those words before.
我知道你们说过
I know you have.
我们都说过
We all have,
只要你曾经历如此沉痛的打击
if you've ever felt so crushing a loss.
今天在座有一对父母
There are two parents with us today
他们了解这种痛苦
who know that pain,
最沉重的伤痛  莫过于
the most terrible hurt of all--
失去一个尚年轻的孩子
losing a child before her time.
如果迪恩和莉安现在站起来
If Dean and Leanne were to stand up right now
吼出那些充满恨意的可怕词句
and scream those awful words of hate,
我们能责怪他们吗
could we blame them?
我做不到
I couldn't.
至少我能理解他们心中的恨
At least their hatred I can understand.
我能体会
I can grasp it,
但上帝的无常
but God's wantonness,
冷酷无情
his cruelty,
我甚至不能...
I can't even begin to--
我的父亲因心脏病猝死
My father dropped dead of a heart attack
年仅43岁  43岁
at the age of 43-- 43 years old--
当他离开时  我仰望上苍
and when he died, I looked up to God
说了这些话
and I said those words,
因为我父亲还如此年轻
because my father was so young,
如此精力充沛  满怀梦想
so full of life, so full of dreams.
为什么上帝要把他夺走
Why would God take him from us?
其实  我并不了解他
Truth be told I never really knew him
也不知道他的梦想
or what his dreams were.
他沉默  胆小 没人在意他
He was quiet, timid, almost invisible.
我的母亲瞧不起他
My mother didn't think much of him.
我外婆讨厌他
My mother's mother hated him.
他根本从未真正地活过
The man never scratched the surface of life.
也许他早逝是件好事
Maybe it's best he died so young.
他没什么贡献  只是占地方罢了
He wasn't doing much but taking up space.
但这样的悼词哪有震撼力  是不是
But that doesn't make for a very powerful eulogy, now, does it?
我流泪  我哭喊  "为什么  上帝"
I wept. I screamed, "Why, God?
我怎能不恨你
How can I not hate you
你从我身边偷走了这个世界上
when you steal from me the person I most love
我最爱最崇敬的人
and admire in this world?
我无法理解  并为此恨你
I don't understand it, and I hate you for it.
《圣经:箴言篇》中写道
The Bible says in proverbs,
"你要专心仰赖耶和华
"Trust in the Lord with all your heart
不可倚靠自己的聪明"
and lean not on your own understanding."
不可倚靠自己的聪明
Lean not on your own understanding.
上帝告诫我们无条件信任他
God is telling us to trust him,
尽管我们无知  仍要爱他
to love him despite our own ignorance.
毕竟  信仰是什么
After all, what is faith
不就是在考验最严峻时依旧能坚持到底吗
if it doesn't endure when we are tested the most?
我们永远不会明白
We will never understand
为什么上帝夺走了杰西卡
why God took Jessica
我的父亲或其他人
or my father or anyone.
虽然上帝没有给我们任何答案
And while God may not give us any answers,
他却赋予了我们爱的能力
he has given us the capacity for love.
我们要做的就是去爱他
Our job is to love him
不去质疑他的安排
without questioning his plan.
所以我恳求您  亲爱的主啊
So I pray to you, dear Lord,
我恳求您
I pray to you
加深我们对您的爱
to help strengthen our love for you
作为回报
and to embrace Dean and Leanne
用您的爱温暖迪恩和莉安
with the warmth of your love in return.
我还恳求您  帮助我们抵御恨意
And I pray that you will help us fend off hatred
让我们能真正地
so that we may all truly
全心全意信任您
trust in you with all our hearts
不倚靠自己的聪明
and lean not on our own understanding.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
你的工作是报道新闻  不是成为新闻
Your job is to report the news, not be the news.
我在推销我们报纸
I was promoting the paper.
你在推销佐伊・巴恩斯
You were promoting Zoe Barnes.
是因为我说我们叫你锤子吗
Is this about how I said we called you the hammer?
如果你是气这个
Because if that upset you,
-我道歉  -这不是重点
- I apologize. - You're missing the point.
我不希望你讲这里的任何事情
I don't want you talking about anything that happens here,
别提昵称  别提我们有多进步
not nicknames, not how progressive we are,
也别提我们是否适应网络时代
not whether we are adapting to the Internet.
你有任何关于这份报纸的想法
Any thoughts you have about this paper,
要么藏在心里  要么告诉我
you keep them to yourself, or you bring them to me.
你不能上国家电视台  然后
You don't get on national television and sp--
抱歉  我没想要
I'm sorry. I wasn't trying to--
我说话的时候别插嘴
Don't interrupt when I'm talking.
你可以像对大人那样跟我说话  汤姆
You can speak to me like an adult, Tom.
不用把我当成小女孩一样教训
You don't have to lecture me like a little girl.
你还不配被当做大人
You haven't earned the right to be treated as an adult.
你以为几篇头版报道  在电视上露几次脸
You think a few front-page stories and some face time on TV
知名美国女记者  曾在《纽约时报》供职
你就是下一位朱迪・米勒了吗
makes you the next Judy Miller?
你还有很长的路要走
You've got a long way to go.
别这么傲慢
Don't be so arrogant.
你认为一个女人要求受到尊重
Okay, so you think when a woman asks to be treated with respect,
是傲慢吗
that's arrogance?
你是说我歧视女性吗
Are you accusing me of sexism?
只是说出我看到的而已
Just making an observation.
一个月不准上电视
No TV for a month.
-什么  -你没听错
- What? - You heard me.
不准接受采访
No interviews.
这不公平
That's completely unfair.
你想永远上不了电视吗
You want to make it no TV indefinitely?
好了  你可以走了
We're done. You can go now.
你好
Hello?
吉莉安  我是克莱尔・安德伍德
Gillian, it's Claire Underwood.
我能上来吗
Can I come up?
你看医生了吗
Have you seen a doctor?
贾弟虫病没那么严重
Giardia's not so bad.
再过一两周就好了
It'll pass in another week or so.
-你没有医疗保险吧  -没有
- You don't have health insurance, do you? - Nope.
我替你预约  你明天去看我的私人医生
I'll make an appointment for you to see my personal GP tomorrow.
药物没有多大作用
Medicine doesn't really do much.
得让它自己好起来
You have to let it run its course.
好吧  那就在适当监控下好起来吧
Well, we'll let it run its course under proper supervision.
别想拒绝我
I won't take no for an answer on this.
-克莱尔 -实在不行  我会亲自拖你去医院
- Claire--  - I'll drag you to the hospital myself if I have to.
你必须去看医生  就这么定了
You're going to the doctor. No argument.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们要走了  完全不听我说
They're about to walk. They won't listen to a word I say.
-两个工会都是吗  -是的
- Both unions? - Yeah.
让马蒂接电话
Put Marty on the phone.
稍等  马蒂
Hang on. Marty.
嗯  是弗兰克吗
Yeah. It's Frank?
这样不行  弗兰克
This isn't working, Frank.
马蒂  你必须让他们留在那里
Marty, you have got to keep them in that room.
他们都没耐心了
They lost their patience.
你不在他们不高兴  弗兰克
They're upset you're not in the room, Frank.
-我下午就回去  -不行  太迟了
- I'll be back this afternoon. - No, it's too late.
听着  告诉他们
Look, tell them
特许学校津贴的事我会妥协
I'll come down on subsidies for charter schools.
即使如此
Even so,
他们对绩效标准非常不满
they're angry about the performance standards.
这还没进行到一半呢
We're not even halfway through this thing.
有许多内容他们
There's so much in it that they--
告诉他们  绩效标准可以商量
Tell them that I'll roll over on performance standards,
频率定为五年一次
five-year intervals.
应该由你来告诉他们  弗兰克
It should be you telling them that, Frank,
你亲自坐在谈判桌前
you here, at this table.
我知道  我在尽我所能
I know that. I'm doing the best I can,
但实在分身乏术
but I can't be in two places at once.
听着  我向你保证
Now, look. I promise you,
如果你把他们留在那里
if you keep them in that room,
我一回去  我们就能克服这个大障碍
we will get through this hump as soon as I get back.
马蒂  你是他们的说客
Marty, you are their lobbyist.
知道什么对他们最好
You know what's best for them.
别让他们作茧自缚
Save them from themselves.
好吧  我想想办法吧
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
斯坦普
Stamper.
死死盯住斯比奈拉
Do not let Spinella out of your sight
有必要的话  就把门锁上
and lock the goddamn doors if you have to.
没问题
You got it.
来了
Here we go.
我知道你是个大忙人  希望我们没妨碍你
I know you're a busy man. I hope we're not keeping you.
不不不  我有的是时间
No, no, no, I've got all the time in the world.
这是鸡肉  这些是火鸡肉
This is ham and these are turkey.
还有些土豆沙拉
And there's some potato salad.
我们做祷告吧
Shall we have a prayer?
仁慈博爱的上帝
Gracious loving God...
你之前得过这种病吗
Have you had this before?
第三次了  我都习惯了
This is the third time. I'm used to it by now.
也不是习惯啦  但比疟疾好受多了
Well, I'm not used to it, but it beats malaria.
你还得过疟疾
You've had malaria.
在津巴布韦时
In Zimbabwe.
病倒一个月
That took me out for a month.
你牺牲了很多啊
You make a lot of sacrifices.
我并不觉得是牺牲
I don't see it as a sacrifice.
你拒绝了谷歌六位数薪水的工作
You turned down a six-figure salary at Google
却做起非营利事业
to start your own non-profit.
在帕洛阿尔托可不会得疟疾
People don't get malaria in Palo Alto.
你做了功课啊
You do your research.
对我在乎的人自然上心
When it's someone I care about.
克莱尔  我拒绝那份工作
Claire, I turned down that job
是因为那样我会恨我自己
because I would've hated myself.
是有很多钱  但为了什么呢
It was a lot of money, but for what?
好让他们用一个上过斯坦福的
So they could fulfill their diversity quota
亚裔女孩来增加公司的多样性吗
with an Asian girl peddling a Stanford degree?
你不是普通的亚洲女孩
Not just any Asian girl.
即毕业时第一名
你致过告别词
A valedictorian.
我能给你谷歌给不了的
Let me offer you what Google couldn't.
我理解你
I know what it is
有能力长得又漂亮  还有雄心
to be capable and beautiful and ambitious
谷歌创始人
谢尔盖和拉里这种人想要你
and be on people like Sergey and Larry's
好用来装点门面
checklist of things that look good to have on a shelf.
我不是来买你的
I'm not trying to acquisition you.
我钦佩你
What I see in you is a woman I admire,
能让我钦佩的女人很少
which doesn't happen often.
我想给你施展的平台
I want to enable you.
我想帮你扫除障碍
I want to clear the way for you
让你能做你想做的事
so that you can achieve what you want to achieve,
按你自己的方式做
on your own terms.
谢谢你的茶
Thanks for the tea.
我明天会派辆车来接你去看医生
And I will send a car to pick you up for the doctor tomorrow.
等你感觉好一点
When you're back on your feet,
你觉得我们可以好好商量一下吗
do you think maybe we can work something out?
是的  我想可以
Yes, I think we could.
这是她在高二舞会上
That's her at junior prom.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
这是她穿着字母夹克衫
Here she is in her letter jacket.
她高一就进了校队
She made varsity as a freshman.
我还记得她知道消息的那一天
I remember the day she found out.
教练打来电话
Coach called.
杰西高兴得蹦了起来
Jessie starts jumping up and down.
"妈  你猜怎么"
"Mom, guess what?"
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不  没事的
Don't be. It's fine.
我们这是在干什么
Why are we doing this?
说真的  回忆这些有什么用
Honestly, what's to be gained in dredging up all this stuff?
回忆美好往事有时能帮助...
Remembering the good things helps sometimes--
让我妻子哭可不叫帮助
Not when it puts my wife in tears.
我感激你在教堂说的那番话
I appreciate what you said at the church,
但对我们没什么用
but it doesn't do us any good.
这也一样
Neither does this.
那我要怎么能帮你们呢
Well, what can I do to help?
你什么都做不了
You can't do anything.
她已经死了
She's gone.
你说得对  这我改变不了
You're right. I can't change that,
但我能确保
but I can make sure
让市政府给你们一笔可观的和解费
the city offers you a sizable settlement.
你是说收买我们
You mean buy us off?
不  我是说帮你们
No, I mean help you
避免旷日持久的官司
avoiding years of court battles.
杰西卡本来要去弗曼上大学  对吗
Jessica was going to go to Furman. Is that right?
她获得了排球奖学金
On a volleyball scholarship?
是的  全额奖学金
Yes, a full ride.
我今早和大学校长谈了
Well, I spoke to the president of the university this morning,
我们想以你女儿的名义创建一个新奖学金
and we'd like to create a new scholarship in your daughter's name.
如果你们愿意的话
If you'd like that.
这完全取决于你们
It's entirely up to you.
但最重要的是
But, most importantly,
我们必须确保这种事故再也不会发生
we have to make sure that this never happens again.
我们拉起了安全广告牌
We've got safety billboards going up,
晚上水塔也不会再亮灯了
we're going to stop lighting the tower at night,
并且在安装护栏
and we're putting the guard rails in.
在她冲下马路前  就该做好这些事
Should've done all that before she ran off the road.
你要我辞职吗  马斯特斯先生
Would you like me to resign, Mr. Masters?
你一句话  我立马辞
Just say the word, and it's done.
如果这能让你好过一点的话
If it will bring you any satisfaction.
我曾问过牧师
I asked the reverend once,
在这些无意义痛苦面前  我们该怎么做
"What are we supposed to do in the face of so much senseless pain?"
他告诉我
And he said to me,
"除了从无意义的事中
"What else can we do
尽力挖掘出一些有意义的东西
but take what seems meaningless
我们还能做什么呢"
and try to make something meaningful from it."
他是对的
He's right.
上帝就是这样
That's how God works--
通过我们发挥作用
through us.
你愿意让我帮助你吗
Will you let me work for you?
你要知道  我的老乡们
What you have to understand about my people
都是高尚的人
is that they are a noble people.
他们的自豪表现在谦逊中
Humility is their form of pride.
这是他们的力量  也是他们的缺陷
It is their strength, it is their weakness,
如果你能在他们面前保持谦卑
and if you can humble yourself before them,
他们会任你差遣
they will do anything you ask.
再跟我们说说奖学金的事
Tell us more about the scholarship.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-工作  -什么工作
- Working. - On what?
军事基地整合委员会的事
The, uh, BRAC commission stuff.
我落进度了
I'm behind on it.
今天是周日
It's Sunday.
所以呢
So?
你周末一般不工作
You don't usually work on the weekend.
现在不是做了
Well, now I do.
厨房里有咖啡  你要吗
There's, uh, coffee in the kitchen. You want some?
彼得
Peter...
Peter.
如果我决定留下来
If I decide to stay,
也是因为我自己  不是因为你
it's because it's what I want, not what you want.
我知道
I understand.
你看的是哪份书面证词的草稿
Which draft are you reading of the written testimony?
你周四发过来的那份
The one you sent on Thursday.
周五我又做了点改动
I actually changed it on Friday.
我指给你看吧
Can I show you?
我想我们可以从工作数量入手
Yeah, I was thinking that we could start with job numbers
接着讲经济乘数
and then go to economic multipliers
而不是倒过来
instead of the other way around.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
改改看吧
Let's see what it looks like.
想象一下
Picture this--
一名17岁的女孩
A 17-year-old girl
以时速60英里驾驶汽车
traveling at 60 miles an hour
在空旷的路上突然失控
spins out of control in no traffic.
然后她撞上了护栏
She hits a guard rail.
但是  如果她系上了安全带
But if she's wearing her seatbelt,
而她确实系了
which she was,
而她的车没有沿着深沟翻了三次
and her car doesn't roll over three times down a 20-foot ditch,
而车的确翻了
which it did,
那么这名女孩现在还会活着
then that young woman is still alive.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
正因为郡长没有建造护栏
The county administrator didn't build those guard rails,
所以她死了
so now she's dead.
我们查了章程
We looked up the statute.
护栏是郡政府管的
Guard rails are under county supervision.
你们想倒打一耙吗
Are you trying to turn this around on me?
这还不止  奥林
That's not all, Orrin.
为了使用自己土地的便利而使用他人土地的权利
还有你的地役权
Your easement.
你看  山麓电网每隔几年
You see, every couple of years the Piedmont Electric,
就申请让输电线横穿加夫尼
they apply to bring power lines through Gaffney.
你这块地正好在路线之上
The route comes right through your lot.
我和吉恩每次都把这事压下
Now, Gene and I always fight them off.
但今年  他们要是再来申请
But this year, if they were to reapply, hmm...
政府强制征收
Eminent domain.
拆掉这么漂亮的房子  真是可惜
It would be such a shame to have to tear down this beautiful home.
见鬼去吧  弗兰克
Fuck you, Frank.
你休想跑到我家来  还一副你的地盘的样子
You can't just roll up on my property and act like you own it.
不  我可以
Oh, but I can.
我已经做了
We just did.
我赢得了这个选区11次选举
I've won this district 11 times.
你以为光凭运气和握手能做到吗
Do you think that's just luck and a firm handshake?
不过告诉你  我不喜欢报复人
But I'll tell you what. I'm not a vindictive person.
要是能达到共赢   我也不忍见任何人输
I don't like for anybody to lose if everybody can win,
所以  我帮你赢得第四选区的选举
so I'm going to help you get elected in the fourth.
你保住房子  我保住第五选区
You get to keep your house. I keep the fifth.
把大桃子抛到脑后  皆大欢喜
We put the Peachoid behind us, and everybody's happy.
你说呢
What do you say?
没关系  你好好考虑吧
Well, that's all right. You think about it.
我相信你会做出正确的选择
I'm sure you'll do the right thing.
期待你成为国会的一员  奥林
Oh, and I'm looking forward to having you in congress, Orrin.
能在对立党派有个朋友总归是好事
It's always good to have friends on the other side of the aisle.
《晚间报道》邀请我去
I've been offered a spot on Nightline.
想听我的建议吗
You want my advice?
不是想  是非常需要
I don't want it. I need it.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
好
Okay.
11点25  《晚间报道》正要开播
So 11:25. Nightline is about to come on.
数以百万计的观众在收看
Millions of people are watching.
你在哪  在家里吗
Where are you, home?
不是
No.
在演播厅吗
At the studio?
是的
Yes.
你看到了什么
And what do you see?
我看到灯光
I see lights.
我看到了摄像头
I see a camera.
上面的小红灯亮了
And that little red dot goes on.
告诉我你听到了什么
Tell me what you hear?
我听见自己的声音
I hear my voice.
观众呢  他们听到了什么
And those millions of people, what do they hear?
我的声音
My voice.
他们看到了什么
And what do they see?
我的脸
My face.
你并不需要我的建议
So you don't need my advice.
汉默施密特会发火的
Hammerschmidt's going to freak.
别在你不想被
You don't want to work anywhere
炒鱿鱼的地方工作  佐伊
you're not willing to get fired from, Zoe.
对我们这类人来说
Treading water's the same
勉强生存与死无异
as drowning for people like you and me.
祝好运  我会盯着你的
Good luck. I'll be watching.
-等等  -怎么了
- Hey, wait. - Yes?
你什么时候回来
When do you get back?
我回来时  你会知道的
When I get back, you'll know.
你好  南茜
Hello, Nancy.
欢迎回来  先生  琳达・瓦斯奎兹找你
Welcome back, sir. Linda Vasquez called for you.
转告她  几小时后我会带着新消息找她
Tell her I'll call her in a couple hours with an update.
-好的  -先生
- Very well. - Sir?
如果不需要别的  凯尔会保护你
Unless you need anything, Kyle has you covered.
不需要  回家吧
No, go home.
这周末你做得很好
You did well this weekend.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
回家之前  能帮我做件事吗
Oh, and before you go home, can you do me a favor?
你能路过我家
Would you swing by my house
把这束花带给克莱尔吗
and make sure these get to Claire?
是  先生
Yes, sir.
先生  谢谢你对我的耐心
And thank you, sir, for being so patient.
好了
Okay.
■
美国的公立教育对所有人包括非法移民的子女都是完全免费的
这给财政造成极大的负担  因而教师的收入微薄
且美国中小学教育不主张用学生成绩来评定教学质量
所以教师是低薪但稳定的工作  这使得公立学校整体教学质量差
这也是剧中总统要进行改革的一个原因
但美国公立教育主要由州政府承办  与联邦政府无关
因为民主党总统最关心的医疗  教育  环保三件事中
医疗改革奥巴马已做过  环保老百姓不关心  才用教育讲故事
■
特许学校就是从政府得到拨款的私立学校
不像传统私立学校那样贵  而教育质量非常好
受美国家长欢迎  而教师工会就非常反对
剧中谈判过程中涉及到对教师进行考核  给特许学校拨款
都是工会非常反对的
美国教师工会的力量非常强大  对民主党有非常大的影响力
教育改革触动教师既得利益  必然受到来自教师工会的阻力
■
本集中提到的"选区"  是特指众议院的选区
美国参议员每州两名  每人任期6年
众议员任期为2年  每州人数根据各州人口按比例分配
一个州被划成若干选区  一个选区选出一个众议员
美国宪法这样的设计  迫使众议员关心选区事务
弗兰克与奥林最后的对话中提到the other side of aisle
国会议事时  两党各坐一边  中间隔着一个过道
所以常用这个短语表达对立党派
翻译  sakura
翻译  某羽
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  妄想的绒布熊
翻译  小蟹
翻译  天意
翻译  ~某人
翻译  小饭
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  音司忐忑
时间轴  吉吉
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第三集
人人影视倾情奉献